On your marks
Get set
Chen Hao
It's really you.
Wait, what are you doing here?
You know why.
How would I kno-
I... I don't know.
I don't even know myself.
Stop playing dumb.
That race...
What the hell did you do?
You did it on purpose that day.
You're overthinking it.
Xie Xin, you might fool others,
but you can't fool me.
Fool you? Why would I? I'm not lying!
That guy
approached me too.
If I don't say anything, and you don't,
no one will ever know.
But Boss Wang...
What do you compete for?
To win, obviously.
And after you win?
After winning, you get attention.
Then you get brand endorsements.
And then you get money.
But can you guarantee that
you'll keep winning until then?
You know how this industry is.
Any single loss
could ruin you forever.
Boss Wang,
Today,
I'm really not here to discuss winning or losing.
I'm here to discuss a new way to make money.
This kind of easy money
won't always be around.
No, why would I drop the baton on purpose?
Chen Hao, we've known each other since middle school.
Then we got into college together.
We've always practiced running together.
I've always been the most competitive one!
I really care about winning.
Don't you know that?
Besides, in competitive sports,
it's very... easy to make mistakes.
You make mistakes if you're too nervous,
and you make mistakes if you're too relaxed.
Get back to your corner.
The match begins!
No, no, no!
That's not what I meant.
We don't need to fight! No need to fight!
Let me just explain this clearly.
I'm telling the truth, Chen Hao!
Tell the truth!
Chen Hao, have you been secretly practicing boxing? I...
You're crazy! I told you the truth!
Listen to me!
Ref! Referee!
Time out! Time out!
I can't see out of my left eye!
I'm telling you, I can't fight anymore!
Why did you make that mistake?
Why would there be a reason for a mistake!
I...
Still making excuses!
Wait! Wait!
Chen Hao! Chen Hao!
I'll tell you the truth.
I didn't want to do match-fixing!
I ran as hard as I could!
But because I was so afraid of making a mistake,
that's exactly why I made one!
Do you understand?
So did you take the money or not?
I didn't!
Bullshit!
Boss Wang,
why are you here?
Don't disappoint me this time either.
What do you mean "either"?
What's this?
Sorry for the trouble.
No, it's not like that.
Thanks for your hard work.
Who? No.
It really wasn't like that.
As agreed.
100,000. The password is your birthday.
Who agreed to anything with you?
Yes, we... we lost the race.
But that was because I was too nervous.
There was a mistake with the baton handoff.
So I let my teammates down,
which caused us to lose.
What does this have to do with...
A pleasure working with you.
No! Who's working with you?
Hold on a second.
I didn't do match-fixing!
I didn't!
It doesn't matter.
We only care about the result.
Why? Says who?
All I had was the process!
I didn't do match-fixing!
It was just a mistake!
Okay, Boss Wang.
Tell me, did you bet on me losing or...
Anyway, that's the situation.
I took the money.
That money...
I wanted to split it among the four of us.
But splitting it would mean admitting to it.
I couldn't admit to it, you know?
Do you understand?
I understand. I get it, I get it.
Do you think we care about your filthy money?
Neck and neck.
You couldn't tell I slowed down early?
Bullshit.
By the way, Xie Xin.
Tell me, if we keep running like this,
will we get anywhere?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I... I don't know either.
By the way, promise me something.
Shoot.
If there ever comes a day
when we become opponents,
make sure you go all out.
Chen Hao!
What?
Neck and neck!
You played me!
Stop right there!
Tell me.
Where did you spend all that money?
Your mom was sick back then, wasn't she?
And medical treatments cost money.
So?
What are you trying to say?
I spent it on her medical bills.
Don't think
that I'll thank you for doing this.
There's no need.
I only gave you the money to make amends.
But you...
But you still broke
our agreement, didn't you?
The score is now 19 to 19.
Tied.
Come on.
Go all out. Come on, get up.
Go all out.
The match is over.
The winner is Chen Hao.
Challenger, please exit.
Shock him.
Xie Xin, you tricked me.
I want a rematch with you.
Get up, Xie Xin.
Xie Xin.
Let's go. Let's go.
No wonder you're so easy to fool.
I think I've figured it out.
This whole setup of yours...
Where is everyone?
A reality show. The Truman Show.
Ex... Ex... Exchange, right?
Very mediocre. Really mediocre.
This piece of junk won't kill me.
I'll give you credit for one thing.
You're really good at digging.
You really did your homework on me.
Digging up my dark past, right?
Bringing in old man Lin, Chen Hao...
I can't even reach these people.
How did you manage to contact them?
But let me just say something.
You're not getting any drama out of me.
No apologies.
No remorse.
No revenge.
No reconciliation.
You're getting absolutely nothing.
Because I'm not a bad guy.
And we aren't enemies.
There's no reason to apologize.
Everything I've done...
I can clearly explain.
I have my logic.
I have my reasons.
Do you hear me?
Who in this world doesn't owe someone a little something?
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
Am I not supposed to be here?
Thank you for setting all this up today, Honey.
I really love it.
You're welcome, Honey.
And thanks to you and him
for coming here.
Did you hear that?
Daddy says thank you to us.
Cheers.
Happy anniversary, Honey.
Happy anniversary.
What's wrong? Why are you looking at me like that?
Handsome.
Is there any compliment...
...about my inner qualities?
Kind.
That doesn't sound cool.
Eloquent.
Deceptive.
A smooth talker.
A... a smooth talker.
W-What's wrong?
Nothing.
A smooth talker.
A very... very smooth talker.
Alright.
Here, this is for you.
Thanks for the compliment.
That was very... very thoughtful.
Happy anniversary, Honey.
Thank you, Honey.
You're welcome, Honey.
What's wrong?
Wait, your finger might be a little swollen.
I bought it too small. You wear mine.
Wear mine. Wear mine.
Right, I'll wear yours. Let's swap.
Here, put it on.
This works, right?
Just wear it like this for now.
You can't wear it on your pinky.
Why not?
The pinky means divorce.
Give it to me, give it to me.
It's fine. It's fine.
It looks good.
It suits you.
Thank you, Honey.
I love it.
What's wrong?
My stomach hurts a little.
Then... then let's go to the hospital.
It's fine, it's fine.
It'll pass in a minute.
We already ordered the food.
Honey, let's go to the hospital to get checked,
then we can eat in peace, okay?
Okay.
Let me, Honey. Give me the bag.
How are you feeling?
I don't feel well.
Still not feeling well, right?
Yeah.
Okay, let's go to the hospital right now.
We'll get you checked up right away.
No, no.
You've been drinking. You need a designated driver service.
Just one sip. Just one sip.
I'm fine. Just trust me, okay?
No, no way.
Trust me. Let's get to the hospital first.
Okay, come on, come on.
It's safer if you get a designated driver service.
Listen to me, the hospital... it's not far.
No.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
I need to sit down for a minute.
Here, come here.
Get in the car, get in, get in.
Come on... okay, okay, okay.
Put your seatbelt on.
Okay.
Okay, just two more turns and we're there.
Car, car, car!
Relax, relax. I see the car.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
I'm watching the road.
Okay, okay, okay. There, there. There, there.
That delivery guy should stay in his own lane! Delivery guys...
Honey, it hurts so much.
It's okay, Honey, it's okay.
Hey man, hey man, hey man!
You... are you okay?
Buddy?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Hey, hey, hey.
Did I hit you?
Don't, don't, don't.
I'm sorry, I was the one
who ran the red light. Be careful.
Can you... can you stand?
Yeah, yeah... I can, I can, I can.
Honey, Honey, Honey!
Here, here, here.
It's okay, it's okay. Let's get in the car.
Let's get in the car.
Don't be scared, don't be scared.
It's okay. Just sit tight, sit tight.
Just sit tight.
Sit tight. Sit tight, sit tight.
Honey, don't move.
I'll buckle your seatbelt.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
It's okay, it's okay.
Let's go, let's go. We're going, we're going.
I'm right here. It hurts!
It's okay, we're almost there.
Almost there, Honey.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Don't be scared, Honey.
I'm right here.
Honey, I'm scared.
The doctor will be right here.
Don't be scared, it's okay.
Family, turn the bed sideways.
Okay, okay. This way, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Is this good? Is this good?
Yes, yes, yes.
Xie Xin! It's okay. Don't be scared, Honey.
Alright, family wait outside.
I'm right here.
Xie Xin, Xie Xin!
I'm here. I'm right here, Honey.
I'll be right here.
Doctor, I...
This is my wife. She's five months pregnant.
You're her family, right?
Yes, yes.
Go get the paperwork done quickly.
Paperwork. Hurry. Okay, okay.
Xie Xin!
Honey, I won't go far.
I'll be right nearby.
You're Zhang Ya's family, right?
She's a bit weak right now,
but it's nothing serious.
It's just that...
we couldn't save the baby.
I... Doc...